Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Leanna Cannonero Papers, 1973-1984 RL.11142
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Leanna Cannonero papers
1973-1984
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11142
0.8 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Leanna Cannonero was an administrative assistant and secretary to JWT President and Chairman Ted Wilson.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Leanna Cannonero papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a [gift/purchase/transfer] in [year].
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following J. Walter Thompson Company Archives collections held in the Hartman Center: Hugh Connell papers, Jack Peters papers, Ted Wilson papers, Information Center Records.
Collection Overview
Collection spans 1973-1984 and includes meeting minutes, memoranda printed reports, financial statements and other printed materials. Main topics include the Chairman's Committee and Survival Anglia, a British television network. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising agencies -- Great Britain; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- Management; J. Walter Thompson Company
- Leanna Cannonero Papers, 1973-1984; 1
  - Chairman's Committee minutes, 1983; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Chairman's meeting agenda and minutes, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Press releases, Greg Bathon resignation and management changes, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Robert Gray litigation, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd., 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd., 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd.--Board of Directors, 1973-1982 (Box 2)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd.--Cameraman's and Production groups, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd.--Executive Committee, 1976-1981 (Box 1)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd.--Executive Committee, 1976-1981 (Box 2)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd.--Financial and Executive Committees, 1976-1978 (Box 2)
  - Survival Anglia Ltd.--Financial reports, 1976-1984; 3 folders (Box 2)